这是账单  ZZ与TOP先生
Here's your check, Mr. ZZ and Mr. Top.
需要打包吗
Would you like a to-go box,
还是直接把吃的收进胡子里
or are you just gonna put it in your beard
跟粘在上面的三明治屑放一起
with the rest of your sandwich?
我们在参加一个蓄胡子比赛
We're in a beard-growing contest.
范围遍布全国各地
They happen all over the country.
还挺盛大隆重的
It's a pretty big deal.
第一名有什么奖
What's first prize?
送你们女友眼罩吗
Blindfold for your girlfriends?
我开玩笑的  我知道你们都是单身狗
I'm kidding, I know you don't have girlfriends.
像这种水平的毛发艺术
Actually, this level of hair-art
是需要数个月的努力与耕耘
takes months of hard work and commitment.
呱  呱  《鸭子王朝》
Well, quack, quack, Duck Dynasty.
我左边的腋毛就能打败你俩
My left armpit could beat you both.
让我代表各地女性告诉你们一件事
Let me tell you something on behalf of women everywhere.
我们  不喜欢  大胡子
We. Don't. Like. Beards.
卡洛琳  大胡子如何[烟幕弹]
Caroline? Beards?
我从来不喜欢当基佬的烟幕弹
I never liked being one.
姑娘们  如果碰到男人叫崔丝
Ladies, if his name is Trace,
就赶紧溜吧
get the hell out of there.
看到没  刮掉吧  废柴们
See? So, shave losers.
就算你们是没下巴  或者下巴太多
If you're chinless or chin-plentiful,
都好过你们现在这副鸟样
it's better than what you've got going on.
这是你们的小费  记得慷慨地报答我
There's your tip, be generous with mine.
你去羞辱人家
You actually insult people
还指望他们会给你钱吗
and then expect them to give you money?
我跟你不就是这样吗
That's how it works with you and me.
谢谢
Thanks.
大家都喜欢我们的小蛋糕T恤
Everyone's loving our new cupcake T-shirts.
刚一个小时我卖了4件
I've sold four in the last hour.
再卖三件  我们就买得起看中的那条毛巾了
Three more and we can afford that towel we've had our eye on.
这些T恤一直有人买买买
These T-shirts keep selling.
就表示钱财会来来来
That means more money.
钱财来代表成功多
Mo' money means mo' success.
成多多
Mo' Success?
我貌似跟他亲戚  钱少少约会过
I think I dated his cousin, Les.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
不介意我在这喘口气吧
Mind if I stop for a breather?
我忙到都"婚"头转向了
I've been "briding" my ass off.
苏菲  这些全都是你的新娘杂志吗
Sophie, are those all your bridal magazines?
这里只有一半
That's only half.
麻利点  奥列格
Come on, Oleg!
这些东西就嫌太重  那你到时候
Look, if those are too heavy, how are you going to be able
怎么有力推着婚礼驴子的屁股过红毯呢
to push the wedding donkey down the aisle?
婚礼驴子吗
Wedding donkey?
我对这婚礼的兴奋度瞬间爆表
My excitement level for this wedding just skyrocketed.
苏菲  请放心
Relax, Sophie.
问世间我会何事  一定就是"推屁股"
If I know how to do anything, it's how to move an ass.
这倒是真的
That's true. Yeah.
你的问题比手上的阿曼达·拜恩斯多了去了
Wow, you're carrying more heavy issues than Amanda Bynes.
你看这些  《美丽新娘》
Look at all these. Beautiful Bride,
《现代新娘》《都市新娘》
Modern Bride, City Bride?
还有  你真的需要这本《非裔美国新娘》吗
And do you really need African American Bride?
我还没删去黑人辫子头的可能性呢
Well, I haven't ruled out cornrows.
黑人辫加驴子吗
Cornrows and a donkey?
请帖回函  参加
RSVP yes.
这个好
Oh, yeah.
这张真辣
This one's hot.
留下来之后"用"
Save that one for later.
我忘了我要结婚了
Oh, I forgot I'm getting married.
留着吧
Keep her.
我周二时可能会想"休战"
I might need a Tuesday off.
苏菲  为什么不请你的伴娘帮忙你呢
Sophie, why don't you get some help from your Maid of Honor?
我会宰了你
I will kill you.
或请个婚礼专家
Or a wedding planner?
苏菲  我的亲戚  斯维特拉娜就是啊
Oh, Sophie, my cousin, Svetlana, is a wedding planner.
好吧  但她最好够厉害
Okay, but she better be good.
因为我想要我的大日子一切完美
Because I want everything to be perfect on my big day.
我们的大日子
Our big day.
你说是就是吧
Yeah. Sure.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
他们都要结婚了  而我的婚礼驴子
They're getting married and I don't have a wedding donkey
还不知道在何方呢
anywhere on my horizon.
额滴天  你们卖这个T恤啊
OMG, you sell these T-shirts?
我刚买了一件
I just bought one.
我是不是前脚卖给你  后脚就忘记了
Did I jut sell you that shirt and already forgot?
我就知道那9分钱的体香剂
I knew that nine-cent deodorant
会对我的大脑造成损伤
was going to give me brain lesions.
标示上的确有个脑子的图
Well, the label did have a picture of a brain
上面标示着西语"不好"啊
with "No Bueno" written on it.
不  我是在曼哈顿一家店买的
No, I bought it at a store in Manhattan
在第九大道东与百老汇那边
on East Ninth and Broadway.
我知道是因为我有强迫症  那里离街角67步
I know because I'm OCD and it was 67 steps
人行道上有14道裂缝
and 14 sidewalk cracks from the corner.
麦克斯  有别人在卖我们的T恤
Max, someone else is selling our shirts.
我知道
I know.
有别的贱人在对我们耍贱招
We're getting hosed by some other hoes.
真不敢相信有人剽窃我们的T恤
I can't believe they stole our shirt.
这是我们做出来唯一一样有人想买的东西
The one thing we made that people actually wanted to buy.
有一种当年"我的空间"的感觉
I feel like Myspace.
我好久没从窗里见过这么令人悲哀的事物
I haven't seen anything this upsetting in a window
上一次还是我不小心看到窗中
since that time I accidentally caught a reflection
自己穿制服的身影
of myself in my waitress uniform.
我们要找人谈谈
We need to talk to someone
你们抄的那些T恤
about those damn shirts you jacked.
我们要发飙了
We about to rumble.
她的意思是  我们想跟人谈一下
What she means is, we wish to speak to someone
你们橱窗卖的那些可爱小蛋糕T恤的事情
about the adorable cupcake T-shirts in the window.
不然我们就要发飙啦
Or, we will be about to rumble.
我只是在这打工好读完
I'm just working here till I get my PhD
我的西方文明生态社会动力学博士学位
in the Eco-Social Dynamics of Western Civilization.
所以要在这打一辈子吗
So, forever?
那些T恤是我们的设计
Those T-shirts are our design
所以我们想知道为什么这里在卖
and we need to know why they're here
还有是谁山寨了我们
and who knocked them off.
是这间店老板的孙女
It's the granddaughter of the woman who owns this shop.
她简直是个恶魔  她现在就走进来了
She's kind of a monster and she's walking in right now.
你们好啊  金柏莉与艾希琳
Hi, Kemberly and Ashlin.
这两位女士对你们的T恤很感兴趣
These ladies are interested in your T-shirts.
很有爱吧
Aren't they cute?
超有爱
So cute.
是啊  超级可爱
Yeah, super cute.
我们设计的
We designed them.
是啊  我们设计的
Yeah, we designed them.
什么
What?
是啊  什么
Yeah, what?
艾希琳与金伯莉是吗
Ashlin and Kimberly, is it?
是金柏莉  是柏
It's Kemberly, with an "E."
我自己改了字  我爱独创
I changed it myself 'cause I'm original.
是啊  她爱独创
Yeah, she's an original.
你们知道什么不是独创的吗
You know what's not original?
那些T恤  是你们从我们那里偷的
Those shirts. You stole them from us.
我们才没偷你们的创意
We did not steal your idea.
是啊  我们才没偷你的创意
Yeah, we did not steal your idea.
我们是山寨布鲁克林的一间烂蛋糕店
We copied it from this lame cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
等等
Wait a minute...
我们就在布鲁克林有间烂蛋糕店
we have a lame cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
艾希琳  你太多话了
Ashlin, you talk too much.
就是因为你  大家才知道我做了胃束带
This is why everyone knows about my lap-band.
我想大家会知道
I think they know about it
是因为你一个春假就瘦了91公斤
because you lost 200 pounds over Spring break.
真不敢相信她曾比现在还让人不爽两倍
It's hard to believe she was once twice this obnoxious.
如果你们不停止卖我们的T恤
If you don't stop selling our T-shirts,
我们就得找我们的律师来处理了
we're gonna have to get our lawyer involved.
是啊  我们会找我们的律师来处理
Yeah, we're gonna have to get our lawyer involved.
他会宰了你们
And he's gonna kill you.
我不知道律师会干嘛
I don't know what lawyers do.
我们完全不是为了自己挣钱
We're totally not doing this for us.
我们是有钱人
We're rich.
是啊  我们有钱
Yeah, we're rich.
每卖出一件T恤  就会有部分钱拿去做慈善
A percentage of every shirt that we sell goes to charity.
是啊  做慈善
Yeah, it goes to charity.
我们俩就是需要被"慈善"的人
We are the charity that it needs to go to.
你们又老又为了钱无下限
You're old and desperate for money.
我完全理解
And I totally get it.
我一个阿姨就是《纽约贵妇的真实生活》里的人
My aunt's one of the Real Housewives of New York.
抱歉  失陪啦
But, sorry.
是没有腿的那个
It's the one without the leg.
刚才发生了什么
What just happened here?
那小姑娘说你老
That girl just called you old.
厄尔  我可能得过阵子才能给你买
Earl, I don't think I'm going to be buying you that pinky ring
你想要的那个尾戒了
you wanted any time soon.
不急  麦克斯  你还有大把时间
No rush Max, you got plenty of time.
我还有足足7  8个月才尘归尘  土归土呢
I got like, six or seven months before I turn to dust.
是因为我们的T恤
It's 'cause our T-shirts got ripped off
被两个曼哈顿的高中女生山寨了
by a couple of prep school girls in Manhattan.
简直像80年代烂电影的剧情
It's like a bad 80's movie.
我都不知道是该跟主角约会
I don't know whether to date James Spader
还是教整个镇子怎么跳舞了
or teach this town how to dance.
真是太不公平了
This is so unfair.
那两女孩不能就这么偷我们的创意
Those girls can't just steal from us.
我们不是想偷就偷的7-11
This isn't 7-Eleven.
麦克斯  真不敢相信你这么天真[西语腔]
Max, I can't believe your naivet.
我用的墨西哥身体喷雾跟这事有啥关系
What does my body spray have to do with anything?
我们不需要为了那两小屁孩而不高兴
Look, there is no reason to be so upset about those two girls.
她们不会影响到我们生意
They're not going to affect our business.
而且她们还得面对自己良心的谴责
Plus, they have to live with themselves.
天理循环  报应不爽
And karma is a bitch.
像我只乱丢过一次垃圾  就沦落成这样了
I mean, I littered once and look what happened to me.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我忙婚礼忙到蛋都要碎了
I'm up to my nuts in bridal junk.
她来了
There she is.
我的一生挚爱
The love of my life.
我是阳你是阴
The yin to my yang.
我是风儿你是沙
The zing to my wang.
把金句留到婚誓的时候念吧
Save that gold for the vows.
我是斯维特拉娜  奥列格的亲戚
I am Svetlana, Oleg's cousin.
亲  还能有更惨的
Well, darling, it could be worse.
比如当他的姐姐或妹妹
You could be his sister.
斯维维
Svetty!
你一定就是苏菲了吧
And you must be Sophie.
是的
Yeah.
不要
No.
你都还没听她的任何点子呢
But you haven't even heard any ideas.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
苏菲  你叫我名字干嘛
Sophie, why did you just say my name?
是奥列格与我的安全词
Oh, it's Oleg's and my safe word.
代表不要
Yeah. It means no.
是唯一我们俩都同意不会在做爱时说出的词
It's the one word we both agreed we would never say during sex.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
每场婚礼我都帮人免费换机油哦
Because I give free oil change with every wedding.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
好吧  我去我的卡座啦
All right, well, I'll be in my booth.
请婚礼专家这事
You know, this wedding planner thing is
跟它的同名电影都一样烂透了
as crappy as the movie of the same name.
姑娘们  忘了跟你们说
Girls, I forgot to tell you,
今天有个男的来把这封信留给你
a man came by today with this letter for you.
这让我想起我曾是个青春的快递界新星
This reminds me of when I was a young, hot-shot courier.
我也曾是个青春的快递界新星
I was a young, hot-shot courier once, too.
骑着我的三轮车送毒品到我妈上班的地方
I used to deliver drugs to my mother at work on my tricycle.
天啊  麦克斯  说了你不会信
Oh, my God, Max, you're not gonna believe this,
那两个姑娘对我们发出了终止令
but those two girls have issued a Cease and Desist order.
那两个贱人
Those bitches.
这是干嘛的
What's that?
上面写着我们得终止贩售我们的T恤
They're saying we have to stop selling our T-shirts.
我当时就跟她们说会对她们这样
That's what I told them we were going to do.
她们连这招都抄了
They even copied this idea.
我们得找个律师
We need to get a lawyer.
怎么找  我们连线上看法律剧都看不起了
How? We can't even afford Law & Order on iTunes.
你觉得我们请得起
Hey, do you think we could afford that lawyer
地铁广告上的那个律师吗
on the subway billboards?
就是一手拿着木槌一手拿着鸡的那个
The one who has a gavel in one hand and a chicken in the other?
他好像只接意外[西语腔]的案子
I think he just does acidentes.
这是怎么回事
What is going on here?
食物在窗口干摆着
There's food waiting in the window,
还有期刊散落四处
periodicals strewn about.
某人也在月事[期刊]里
Someone's on his periodical.
阿憨  我们收到传票[服务]了
Han, we just got served.
至少咱们餐厅有人得到服务了
At least someone in the diner has.
你们该庆幸你们老板很冷静
You're lucky your boss is so chill.
你当然"冷静"啦  你是波普先生的企鹅
Of course you're chill, you're one of Mr. Popper's penguins.
这样呢
How about this?
我们会做你已经付钱给我们的工作
We'll do the jobs you already pay us for
只要你同意假扮成我们的律师
if you agree to pretend to be our lawyer.
你有西装的对吧
You have a suit, right?
我为什么要假扮成律师呢
Why would I pretend to be a lawyer?
你们连服务员都假扮不了
You can't even pretend to be waitresses.
反正不会有人相信阿憨是我们的律师
No one's gonna believe Han's our lawyer, anyway.
他考不过司法考[吧台]  身高都没吧台高
He can't pass the bar, he can barely see over one.
够了  我受够你俩以及你们的懒鬼态度
That's it! I've had it with you two and your non-work ethic.
这一区是给客人坐的
And this area is for customers.
把这些东西给我拿开
I want these out of here!
麦克斯
Max?
我应该能翻出一件西装吧
I suppose I could dig up a suit if that could, somehow,
只要这件老板攻击员工的事能就此过去
make this boss striking his employee thing go away.
麦克斯  那两女孩来这间学校完全不意外
Max, of course these girls go to Dalby Hall,
我以前的宿敌也都是
all my archenemies did.
最后的赢家看来是雷帝嘎嘎
I guess Lady Gaga won in the end, though.
告诉你个其他消息  姐挺喜欢这眼罩
In other news, I kind of like this eye-patch.
我知道啊  你刚才假装自己是
I know you do, you were pretending to be
地铁的"铁"盗女王
the pirate queen of the subway.
谁敢说不是呢[海盗腔]
Well, no one arrrrrgued with us.
眼科医生说这玩意儿得戴多长时间啊
How long did the eye doctor say you have to keep it on?
我说的眼科医生是指那个收了我们免费甜点的
And by eye doctor, I mean that first-year med student
那个大一的医科学生
we gave the free dessert to.
得几天吧  真不够劲
A few days, which is a bummer,
因为眼睛减半  惨况也减半了
'cause only seeing half of how sad we are
所以算是福气加半呢
is kind of a blessing.
我们要怎么找到她们呢
How are we gonna find them?
循着我们T恤帝国腐朽没落的气味吗
Follow the scent of our decaying T-shirts business?
根据图片分享网  她们在食堂呢  看见了吗
According to Instagram, they're in the cafeteria, see?
艾希琳刚上传了一张迷你披萨的照片
Ashlin just posted a pic of a mini-pizza.
标题是披萨人生
#thatpizzalife
这里居然有迷你披萨
They have mini-pizzas here?
我的高中连暖气都没有
My high school didn't even have heat.
抱歉  我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我得去便宜男士服饰店买套西服
I had to pick up a suit at the Men's Warehouse.
你说的应该是男童服饰店吧
Don't you mean the Not Quite A Man's Warehouse?
阿憨  我喜欢你这身律师装  感觉跟真的一样
Han, I love your lawyer costume. So authentic.
唯一缺少的是出卖灵魂后  剩下的空洞
Only thing missing is the hole where your soul should be.
正如我平常所说  如果你决心要做一件事
Well, as I always say, if you're going to do something--
记得用左手  这样感觉会像是别人的手
Do it with your left hand so it will feel like someone else?
错  如果你决心要去做  就一定要做好
No, if you're going to do something, do it right.
去年万圣节  我扮成绿巨人广告中的小绿芽
Last Halloween, I went as Sprout from the Green Giant commercial
我特别还用豆荚挡住了我的小鸡鸡
and I even put pea pods over my pee-pee.
你们尽管笑  但哥赢了500块呢
You laugh, but I won $500.
行啦  我已经把咱们的终止令做好了
Okay, I created my own Cease and Desist order.
这玩意你从哪儿弄的
Where did you get this?
跟麦克斯打印那张假的
Same place Max printed out that fake,
"我没有性病"的医生证明是同一地方
"I don't have herpes" doctor certificate.
超管用的
It works.
这是你的名片
And here's your business card.
手呢  手在哪里
Where? Where is it?
我看不见
I can't see.
这里
Here.
阿憨  但愿你的演技比麦克斯好
And Han, I hope you're a better actor than Max.
巨石强森的演技都比麦克斯好了
Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson is a better actor than Max.
鲁诉先生
Mr. Lu Su?
你就想出这种烂名字吗
That's what you came up with?
鲁诉先生
Mr. Lu Su?
你是个律师啊  所以"诉"这个字恰到好处
Well, you're a lawyer, so the "Su" part is totally on point.
可鲁诉这个名字
But Lu Su?
亚洲人才不会起这种烂名字呢
No Asian was ever named that.
或许这个银河系里没有
Maybe not in this galaxy,
但我可以提醒你  有个亚洲人叫苏鲁先生
but might I remind you of a Mr. Sulu.
没错  我就换了换位置  天才吧
Oh, yeah. I mixed it up. Genius!
阿憨  你不一定要拿出你的名片
Han, you don't have to use the cards.
我一定能演好
I can make it work.
两个万圣节前  我曾扮演伊沃克人
Two Halloweens ago, I was an Ewok
把一块橙色的浴巾变成了穆斯林的头巾
and turned an orange bath-towel into a turban.
第二名  赢了250块
Second place. $250.
下一个万圣节  你可以穿着这身衣服
And next Halloween, you can wear that
说自己扮的是女同性恋牧师
and goes as a lesbian minister.
好啦  我们的计划是进去
Okay, so the plan is, we go in there
在律师的陪同下  冷静地跟她们对质
and calmly confront them with our attorney.
我来发言
I'll do the talking.
阿憨  你就在一边站着  装聪明人
Han, you stand there and try to look smart.
我是亚洲人  这点妥妥的
Ah. I'm already Asian. So, done.
哇  这画面想起从前
Wow, this brings me back.
我的专座遍布于受欢迎女生组
I had a seat at the popular table,
辩论队组  学生会组
the Debate Team table, the Student Council table,
以及婚前守贞组
and the Waiting For Marriage table.
但守贞组后来四分五裂
But that table kind of fell apart
因为除了我  其他人都怀孕了
when everybody got pregnant but me.
我高中时都是跟一个酒鬼在学校停车场吃饭
I ate in the school parking lot with a wino.
他当时对我很好  我还以为他可能是我爸
He was so nice to me, I thought he might be my dad.
但他从未对我动手动脚
But then he never made a move on me,
所以我猜应该不是
so I guess he wasn't.
各位请注意  请注意
Attention everyone, attention.
是啊  各位请注意  请注意
Yeah, attention everyone, attention.
今天我和艾希琳不但是来卖我们的T恤
Ashlin and I are here today to sell our T-shirts
还要谈谈"欺凌"这个问题
and to talk about bullying
以及这样真的不酷
and how it's not cool.
超级不酷
It's so not cool.
我在说话呢  艾希
I was talking, Ash.
是啊  她在说话呢
Yeah, she was talking.
她们的慈善主题居然是反欺凌
Their charity is bullying?
感觉就像侃爷想为自己的低调筹款一样
That's like Kanye West trying to raise money for laying low.
每卖出一件我们超级无敌可爱T
A $3 donation will be made to our anti-bullying fund
就会有3块钱捐到我们反欺凌基金会
with each purchase of one of our super, super cute tees.
超级无敌可爱T
Super, super cute tees.
是老娘的超级无敌可爱T
My super cute tee!
我这辈子最棒的点子
Best idea I ever had.
能与之并列的就只有能绑下巴的大麻烟斗
Right up there with the bong with a chin strap
这样就有手可以按遥控器换台了
so you could be hands-free to change the channel.
大家先买T恤  我们晚点再继续
So buy a shirt right now and then we'll be back later
我们的反欺凌演讲
for the rest of the anti-bully talk.
是啊  大家快买  否则我爸今年
Yeah, buy them or my dad won't pay
不会花钱给学校买曲棍球器材哦
for the lacrosse equipment this year.
找她们算账
Let's go.
她们靠卖我们的点子发大财
They are making a fortune on us.
要栽跟斗  也不能栽在未满21岁的小毛孩手上
And if I'm gonna get screwed, it better be by someone over 21
听起来只需喝几杯酒  你就会乖乖被人骗
Yeah, that sounds like a job with a two drink minimum.
阿憨  你可别搞砸  否则我让你把眼镜吞了
Han, don't mess this up or you'll be eating those glasses.
你想不想看看反欺凌的宣传手册啊
Might I interest you in an anti-bullying pamphlet?
你想不想看我对你竖中指啊
Might I interest you in a seat on my finger?
你们俩怎么进来的
Hey, how did you two get in here?
学校花钱请保安看门  就是不让流浪汉随便进来
The school pays guards out front to keep out the homeless.
是啊  傻了吧
Yeah, well, jokes on you.
因为保安拦都没拦我们
'Cause they just let us walk in.
两位小姑娘  你们现在就可以
Hello, girls. You can "Cease and Desist"
"终止"贩卖我们的T恤了
selling our T-shirts as of now.
这位是我们的律师
This is our attorney, Mr....
鲁诉先生
Lu Su.
他手里也有一份我们针对你们终止令
And he is holding our Cease and Desist
量身定做的终止令
to counter your Cease and Desist.
好吧  首先你们的律师
Okay, well, first, your lawyer
看起来像迪士尼儿童节目的老师
looks like a teacher on a Disney show.
这是坏事吗
Is that a bad thing?
其次  如果你还有什么话要说
And if you have anything further to say,
你可以找我的律师谈  也就是她爸
you can take it up with my lawyer. Her dad.
我爸超厉害哦
And he's real good.
他根据一个技术细节问题  就让一名CEO承认
He got that CEO guy who admitted he killed his whole family
自己杀害了整个家族
out on a technicality.
我忘了坏女孩能有多贱
I forgot how mean girls can be.
哪可能忘  你天天看得到我
How? I'm your roommate.
谢谢  金柏莉  谢谢  艾希琳
Thank you, Kemberly. Thank you, Ashlin.
帮帮忙
A little help.
大家好  姑娘们  你们都是好人
Hello, girls, you all look very nice.
他要干什么呀
What is he doing?
希望扯个10分钟后  他能扯到主题吧
Hopefully a tight ten and then he'll bring up the headliner.
这话说出来可能有点难以置信  大家看着我
This may be hard to believe, looking at me
西装革履  衣冠楚楚
in this totally awesome suit,
但我对于被人欺凌略有了解
but I know a little something about being bullied.
当我还是个小孩
As a little child--
现在也只是个巨婴
And as a slightly bigger adult.
你不是吧
Seriously?
人家在发表欺凌演讲  你还要欺负他
In the middle of his bullying speech, your bullying?
连我自己都惊讶了
Kind of surprised even myself.
有个人总是欺负我
I have someone who bullies me.
得  趁现在还能走  快溜
Okay, let's get out of here while I can.
对我不仅仅是拳打脚踢和辱骂嘲弄
It's not just the hitting and the name-calling.
虽然老实说  那真的让人很不爽
Although, not gonna lie, that's a real bummer.
但姑娘们  受欺凌最可怕的其实是
You see, girls, the bad thing about being bullied
每一次当你被欺负时
is that every time it happens,
仿佛有一小部分的自我被偷走了
it steals a little piece of who you are.
于是随着次数增多  慢慢地
And then, if it happens enough, little by little,
你会变得越来越不像原本的自己
you become just a little less of who you were meant to be.
这样真的不酷
And that's not cool.
而台上这两位小女孩  我确定在不知不觉中
And these two girls up here, without knowing it, I'm sure,
"偷"走了一小部分的麦克斯和卡洛琳
stole a little piece of Max and Caroline.
因为你们偷走了她俩的小创意
when they stole their little idea.
这样超级不酷
And that's so not cool.
是啊  这样超级不酷
Yeah, that's so not cool.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  我们会终止T恤的制作
Max, Caroline, we'll stop making the shirts.
艾希  我可没那么说
Ash, I never said that.
不  金柏莉  我说了算
Ah, no, Kemberly. I did.
我更喜欢做胃束带前的你
And I liked you more before the lap-band.
当时你还叫金伯莉  伯母的"伯"
When you were still Kimberly with an "I."
麦克斯  阿憨刚才是救了咱俩吗
Max, did Han just save us?
我没在听  我在偷藏迷你披萨进口袋呢
I wasn't listening, I was putting mini-pizzas in my pocket.
姑娘们  你们上班迟到40分钟了
Girls, your shift started 40 minutes ago.
今天来这么早干嘛
What are you doing here so early?
厄尔  好消息  我们现在是所有
Earl, good news. We are now the sole owners
小蛋糕T恤的唯一拥有者
of all those cupcake T-shirts.
说真的  这也是我们唯一拥有的
And, literally, nothing else.
或许我可以租一个鹦鹉
Maybe I could rent a parrot
去海滋客打打工
and pick up some shifts at Long John Silver's.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我准备要见我的婚礼专家了
I'm about to meet another wedding planner.
这次这个一定很棒
And this one's gonna be good!
因为他是基佬
He's gay.
苏菲·科臣斯基
Sophie Kuchenski?
果然是你  天啊
Yes, God!
从刚进门那一刻开始  我就对自己说
From the second I walked in here, I said to myself,
"一定是她"  我一眼就看出来了
"That has to be her." And I can see it.
我们要一起创造奇迹哦
We're going to make magic together.
是啊  基佬里的"不"该怎么说
Yeah, what's gay for no?
好吧
Okay.
基佬龙卷风袭过  我们好像活下来了
Wow, I think we just survived a "torgaydo."
我要去哪里再找一个基佬婚礼专家呢
Where am I gonna find another gay wedding planner
纽约这么大
in New York now?
你可以去连锁家居店里大发脾气
Just throw a tantrum in a Crate & Barrel,
会有五个基佬跑过来问你怎么了
and five of them will come running.
今天的法律工作干得不错嘛
Hey, nice legal work today.
你应该上《小人民法庭》这档节目
You should be on the Little People's Court.
是啊  从现在开始  我要称你为"憨尼·柯克伦"
Yeah, from now on, I'm calling you "Hanny Cochran."
好吧  下次你们要是想谢谢我
Okay. Next time you want to thank me,
送我一篮水果花就行
just send me an Edible Arrangement.
我不懂到底要暗示多少次才行呀
I don't know many times I have to drop that hint.
你的暗示太"小"  看不太见
But that's just, like, a two-inch drop.
抱歉  我情不自禁
Sorry. I can't help myself.
但我会努力  因为我知道那天你演讲里
But I'm going to try because I know I was the bully
那个欺负你的人是我
you were talking about in that speech.
什么  我说的是我们楼里那个女门卫
What? I was talking about the doorwoman in my building.
我想拿信件  就必须得让她捏爆我的咪咪头
I have to submit to a purple-nurple just to get my mail.
还有其他女人欺负你吗
There's another woman?
麦克斯  我想阿憨有恶霸小三
Max, I think Han has a side bully.
好吧  看来我得使劲欺负你了
Well, I'll just have to try harder.
因为如果你是被人无情地捏咪咪头
Because if anyone is gonna mercilessly nurple you
而过早死去  那个人也必须是我
into an early grave, it's got to be me.
我也希望是这样  麦克斯
I'd like to think so, Max.
你还想坐车时  不用坐婴儿椅呢
You'd also like to ride in a car facing forwards.
恢复正常
Back to normal.